Brent Terry

Orlando, FL 32751 • bterryconsulting@gmail.com • (904) 309-0158

Summary

Brent is a Robotic Process Automation Consultant with industry experience in TMT, Energy (Nuclear), and the Department of Homeland Security. He is passionate about client success and the development of custom solutions to drive continuous improvement and innovation for clients on their Digital Transformation journey.

Professional Experience

Deloitte Consulting, Orlando, FL

Solution Specialist | June 2020 - Present Solution Analyst | July 2018 - June 2020

- Identifying automation strategies for customers by analyzing and documenting current business processes, outlining requirements, creating process flow models, and developing automations for customers in various sectors
- Created custom solution using python 3.6 to solve complex client need which resulted in 15x efficiency gain
- Delivers end-to-end solutions and maintenance for high quality software and RPA Bots
- Discovers new and innovative tools to further accelerate development timelines
- Communicates effectively with client business leaders in correlation to their automation strategies and timelines

Gravity IT Resources, Ft. Lauderdale, FL

IT Talent Agent | May 2017 – July 2017

- Administered and evaluated candidate proficiency exams in programming languages such as Python, Javascript, Java, C++, and C#
- Utilized Bullhorn Applicant Tacking System to aggregate, manage, and record candidate data
- Managed communications with Fortune 500 hiring managers to evaluate candidates for placement
- Marketed Gravity IT Human Resources services to prospective clients
- Led office in successful candidate placements over duration with firm

Skills

- UiPath 2018, 2018.4.4 (Certified)
- Automation Anywhere 10.5, 11
- Python, C#
- Understanding of NLP and Chatbots (Kore.AI)
- Microsoft SQL Server Database (SSMS)
- Microsoft Office Excel, Powerpoint, Word, Access, Visio
- Active Top Secret security clearance
- Active Public Trust security clearance

Education

Florida State University, Tallahassee, FL

Bachelor of Science, Management Information Systems | May 2018